let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Machines running LISP are also called?",
        answer: "A. AI Workstations",
        options: [
            "A-: AI Workstations",
            "B-: Regression",
            "C-: Both A and B",
            "D-: Time series prediction",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Identify the language which is used in data science?",
        answer: "D. Ruby ",
        options: [
            "A-: C++",
            "B-: R",
            "C-: Java",
            "D-: Ruby",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "In which language is Hadoop written?",
        answer: "B. Java",
        options: [
            "A-: C++",
            "B-: Java",
            "C-: Python",
            "D-: All of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Machine learning is a subset of which of the following_____",
        answer: "A. Artificial intelligence",
        options: [
            "A-: Artificial intelligence",
            "B-: Deep learning",
            "C-: Data learning",
            "D-: None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Total groups in which data can be characterized is?",
        answer: "B. 2",
        options: [
            "A-: 1",
            "B-: 2",
            "C-: 3",
            "D-: 4",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which of the following is not a part of the data science process?",
        answer: "A. Communication building",
        options: [
            "A-: Communication building",
            "B-: Operationalize",
            "C-: Model planning",
            "D-: Discovery",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Identify the key data science skills among the following______",
        answer: "D. All of the above",
        options: [
            "A-: Data visualization",
            "B-: Machine learning",
            "C-: Statistics",
            "D-: All of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Identify whether true or false: Qubole is a big data tool______",
        answer: "A. True",
        options: [
            "A-: True",
            "B-: False",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Data in___________bytes is called big data",
        answer: "D. Peta",
        options: [
            "A-: Meta",
            "B-: Giga",
            "C-: Tera",
            "D-: Peta",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Big data analysis does the following except?",
        answer: "B. Analyze data",
        options: [
            "A-: Spreads data",
            "B-: Analyze data",
            "C-: Organizes data",
            "D-: Collect data",
        ]
    }
];